<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Minyan Mate</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    
    <string name="title_active_minyan">Active</string>
    <string name="title_edit_minyans">Edit Minyans</string>
    
    
    <string name="tos">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service">
        <![CDATA[
        <h2>Minyan Mate Terms of Service</h2>
        
        <p>Last Updated: December 3 2013</p>
        
        <p>These terms of service ("Terms") apply to your access and use of 
        Minyan Mate (the "Service"). Please read them carefully.</p>
        
        <h3>Accepting these Terms</h3>
        
        <p>If you access or use the Service, it means you agree to be bound by
         all of the terms below. So, before you use the Service, please read 
         all of the terms. If you don\'t agree to all of the terms below, please 
         do not use the Service.</p>
         
        <h3>Privacy</h3>
        
        <p>We do not transmit or store your data outside of your device. Data
        from your device may be used in providing the Service and stored locally, but 
        is not otherwise transmitted or copied.</p>
        
        <h3>Conduct</h3>
        
        <p>The Service facilitates messaging individuals in order to arrange "minyans"
        and to ascertain a headcount. You may not use the Service to send
        unsolicited, political, or commercial messages to other parties.</p> 
        
        <h3>Miscellaneous</h3>
        
        <p>Standard carrier messaging charges may apply.</p>
        
        <h3>Unavoidable Legal Stuff</h3>
        
        <p>THE SERVICE AND ANY OTHER SERVICE AND CONTENT INCLUDED ON OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE 
        TO YOU THROUGH THE SERVICE ARE PROVIDED TO YOU ON AN AS IS OR AS AVAILABLE BASIS WITHOUT
		ANY REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND. WE DISCLAIM ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES AND 
		REPRESENTATIONS (EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, ORAL OR WRITTEN) WITH RESPECT TO THE SERVICE AND 
		CONTENT INCLUDED ON OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU THROUGH THE SERVICE WHETHER ALLEGED 
		TO ARISE BY OPERATION OF LAW, BY REASON OF CUSTOM OR USAGE IN THE TRADE, BY COURSE OF DEALING OR OTHERWISE.</p>

		<p>IN NO EVENT WILL ITS DEVELOPERS BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY SPECIAL, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
		 EXEMPLARY OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SERVICE OR ANY OTHER 
		 SERVICE AND/OR CONTENT INCLUDED ON OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU THROUGH THE SERVICE, 
		 REGARDLESS OF THE FORM OF ACTION, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, 
		 EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES OR ARE AWARE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF 
		 SUCH DAMAGES. OUR TOTAL LIABILITY FOR ALL CAUSES OF ACTION AND UNDER ALL THEORIES OF LIABILITY WILL BE 
		 LIMITED TO THE AMOUNT YOU PAID TO ITS DEVELOPERS. THIS SECTION WILL BE GIVEN FULL EFFECT EVEN IF ANY 
		 REMEDY SPECIFIED IN THIS AGREEMENT IS DEEMED TO HAVE FAILED OF ITS ESSENTIAL PURPOSE.<p>

		 <p>You agree to defend, indemnify and hold us harmless from and against any and all costs, damages,
		 liabilities, and expenses (including attorneys\' fees, costs, penalties, interest and disbursements) we 
		 incur in relation to, arising from, or for the purpose of avoiding, any claim or demand from a third party 
		 relating to your use of the Service or the use of the Service by any person using your account, 
		 including any claim that your use of the Service violates any applicable law or regulation, or the rights 
		 of any third party, and/or your violation of these Terms.</p>]]>
    </string>

</resources>
